The American dream just keeps getting more expensive.
Generation Wealth is a documentary film directed by Lauren Greenfield.
Over the past 25 years, Lauren Greenfield's documentary photography and film
projects have explored youth culture, gender, body image, and affluence.
Underscoring the ever-increasing gap between the haves and the have-nots, portraits reveal a focus on cultivating image over substance,
where subjects unable to attain actual wealth instead settle for its trappings, no matter their ability to pay for it.
Self - Interviewer, played by Lauren Greenfield.
Self, played by Florian Homm.
Self, played by Bret Easton Ellis.
Self, played by Kim Kardashian.
Self, played by Kylie Jenner.
Self, played by Eden Wood.
Generation Wealth is a 2018 American documentary
film directed by Lauren Greenfield.
It follows Greenfield's 2017 book and photo exhibition of the same name.
The film explores themes of capitalism, materialism,
consumerism, late stage capitalism.